### SUSHMA SRIMATHTIRUMALA ( premium )





Software Developer with 4+ years of experience in Data Structures Algorithms, Java, Design pattern development. experience in Java spring RESTful API webservi, Angular html css java script kubernetes, Google cloud platform Angular MySQL, POSTGRE.NoSQL



Current Designation: Senior Consultant Total Experience: 5 Year(s) 5 Month(s)

Current Company: Ernst and Young Services Pvt. Ltd Notice Period: 1 Month

Current Location: Hyderabad / Secunderabad Highest Degree: PGCPF [Finance]

Pref. Location: Mumbai, Bengaluru / Bangalore, Hyderabad Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Project Management, Algorithm Development, System Analysis, SQL, Spring, Javascript, MySQL, java developer, GCP, Core Java, JDBC, Cloud

Computing, Java, Rest, C++, Microservices, Data Structures

Verified: Email - id Phone Number |

Last Active: Jan-Mar 2021 Last Modified: Jan-Mar 2021

# Summary

Software Developer with 5+ years of experience in Data Structures and Algorithms, Design patterns, Java, product and application development. experience in Java spring angular html css java script kubernetes, Google cloud platform. Along with MySQL, postgre database, Oracle DB, Unix, C/C++, Agile methodology. Cloud Computing with kubernetes, Collections, Multithreading, REST API, microservices, spring boot, RESTful webservices, GCP

# **Work Experience**

Ernst and Young Services Pvt. Ltd as Senior Consultant Oct 2020 to Till Date

Developer

CDK Global as Senior Member Technical Staff

Mar 2019 to Oct 2020

Drive Management System: Working in the end to end product development of Auto line Drive

Skills: Core Java, Angular, SQL, mySQL, Oracle SQL, Spring, JavaScript, GCP GOOGLE CLOUD PLATFORM

Worked as a developer with programming language as Java, Data Strucures and Algorithms. Developed both front-end as well as back-end

Working in the module of CRM customer flow for the car dealership software

Designed and developed the application and customized it for the OEM manufacturers like Porsche UK, Volkswagen and

Adhered to the spirit timelines and delivered the user stories with quality

Efficiently solved bugs present in the current application as well

#### Wipro Technologies as Software Engineer

May 2015 to Mar 2019

Skills: Core Java, Angular, SQL, mySQL, Oracle SQL, Spring, JavaScript

Firefly(Jan'18-Present) Client: CITI BANK

Development of Firefly application in Java programming for various branches across the countries in the Asia Pacific (APAC) and Europe and Middle East (EMEA) regions.

The Firefly is an application interface used by the Citi branches for the Dip card, Greet, pin pad, for amount transactions and for printing the receipt functionalities.

CPI (Mar'16 - Dec'17)

Client: Ericsson

The project is to design and deploy the tools for the Customers in order to access the Customer Product Information in a structured way and deliver to the end users.

As a designer, I am responsible for the development of the web application. I have used HTML, JavaScript, Angular for front-end development and Java ,SQLfor back end

Used Unix shell scripting for server side log monitoring.

FMD (Dec'15-Mar'16)

Client : Apple

The project is to ensure website of FMD is robust and free from defects. I have worked in all phases of STLC.

Designed test cases for each test scenarios of the website. Used JUnit for the Unit testing Java components used at the server side.

Worked as QA and QE engineer for the end-to-end website and contributed in the UAT to ensure that the website is delivered on time to the customer.

RPS design (May'15 - Nov'15)

Client: Ericsson

The project is on telecom network architecture of GSM and GPRS. It deals with the development of switching platform and the nodes of the network called AXE

As a developer I was responsible for handling the design problem in nodes of RPS subsystem on Unix platform using C language.

### **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computer Science and Engineering) from K L University in 2015

PG: PGCPF (Finance) from Indian Institute of Management (IIM), Indore in 2018

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

Unix Workbench

**IBM Data Science** 

Google Cloud Platform

#### IT Skills

| Skill Name                | Version | Last Used | Experience           |
|---------------------------|---------|-----------|----------------------|
| C, C++, Java , J2EE       |         |           | 3 Year(s) 0 Month(s) |
| CSS , Javascript , HTML5  |         |           |                      |
| MySQL                     |         |           |                      |
| UNIX, WINDOWS             |         |           |                      |
| MS-Office,NetBeansIDE-7.1 |         |           |                      |
| Shell Scripting           |         |           | 2 Year(s) 9 Month(s) |
| JUNIT                     |         |           |                      |
| CORE JAVA                 | 8       |           | 3 Year(s)            |
| AngularJs                 |         |           | 2 Year(s)            |
| Shell Scripting           |         |           | 2 Year(s) 0 Month(s) |

# Languages Known

 $1/22/2021 \\ https://freesearch.naukri.com/preview/printResume?uname=94402299328f0219502813313a58d39e0a0b5a051e145f44054210585d...$ 

| Language | Proficiency | Read | Write | Speak |
|----------|-------------|------|-------|-------|
| English  |             |      |       |       |
| Hindi    |             |      |       |       |
| Tamil    |             |      |       |       |
| Telugu   |             |      |       |       |

## **Affirmative Action**

Category: General

Physically Challenged: No

## **Work Authorization**

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time